[0, 0, "Text string indicating the entity type (fixed)"],
[1, 1, "Primary text value for an entity"],
[2, 2, "Name (attribute tag, block name, and so on)"],
[3, 4, "Other text or name values"],
[5, 5, "Entity handle; text string of up to 16 hexadecimal digits (fixed)",
[6, 6, "Linetype name (fixed)"],
[7, 7, "Text style name (fixed)"],
[8, 8, "Layer name (fixed)"],
[9, 9, "DXF: variable name identifier (used only in HEADER section of the DXF file)"],
[10, 10], "Primary point; this is the start point of a line or text entity, center of a circle, and so on \n" +
  "DXF: X value of the primary point (followed by Y and Z value codes 20 and 30) \n" +
  "APP: 3D point (list of three reals)"],
[11, 18, "Other points \n" +
  "DXF: X value of other points (followed by Y value codes 21-28 and Z value codes 31-38) \n" +
  "APP: 3D point (list of three reals)"],
[20, 20, "DXF: Y value of the primary point"],
[30, 30, "DXF: Z value of the primary point"],
[21, 28, "DXF: Y values of other points"],
[31, 37, "DXF: Z values of other points"],
[38, 38, "DXF: entity's elevation if nonzero"],
[39, 39, "Entity's thickness if nonzero (fixed)"],
[40, 47, "Double-precision floating-point values (text height, scale factors, and so on)"],
[48, 48, "Linetype scale; default value is defined for all entity types"],
[49, 49, "Multiple 49 groups may appear in one entity for variable-length tables (such as \n" + 
  "the dash lengths in the LTYPE table). A 7x group always appears before the first 49 group \n" +
  "to specify the table length"],
[50, 58, "Angles (output in degrees to DXF files and radians through AutoLISP and ObjectARX applications)"],
[60, 60, "Entity visibility; absence or 0 indicates visibility; 1 indicates invisibility"],
[62, 62, "Color number (fixed)"],
[66, 66, "Entities follow flag (fixed)"],
[67, 67, "0 for model space or 1 for paper space (fixed)"],
[68, 68, "APP: identifies whether viewport is on but fully off screen; is not active or is off"],
[69, 69, "APP: viewport identification number"],
[70, 78, "Integer values, such as repeat counts, flag bits, or modes"],
[90, 99, "32-bit integer values"],
[100, 100, "Subclass data marker (with derived class name as a string). Required for all objects and entity \n" +
  "classes that are derived from another concrete class. The subclass data marker segregates data \n" +
  "defined by different classes in the inheritance chain for the same object. \n" +
  "This is in addition to the requirement for DXF names for each distinct concrete class derived \n" +
  "from ObjectARX (see Subclass Markers)"],
[102, 102, "Control string, followed by &quot;{&lt;arbitrary name&gt;&quot; or &quot;}&quot;. \n" + 
  "Similar to the xdata 1002 group code, except that when the string begins with &quot;{&quot;, \n" + 
  "it can be followed by an arbitrary string whose interpretation is up to the application. \n" + 
  "The only other control string allowed is &quot;}&quot; as a group terminator. \n" + 
  "AutoCAD does not interpret these strings except during drawing audit operations. \n" + 
  "They are for application use."],
[105, 105, "Object handle for DIMVAR symbol table entry"],
[110, 110, "UCS origin (appears only if code 72 is set to 1); DXF: X value; APP: 3D point"],
[111, 111, "UCS Y-axis (appears only if code 72 is set to 1); DXF: Y value; APP: 3D vector"],
[112, 112, "UCS Z-axis (appears only if code 72 is set to 1); DXF: Z value; APP: 3D vector"],
[120, 122, "DXF: Y value of UCS origin, UCS X-axis, and UCS Y-axis"],
[130, 132, "DXF: Z value of UCS origin, UCS X-axis, and UCS Y-axis"],
[140, 149, "Double-precision floating-point values (points, elevation, and DIMSTYLE settings, for example)"],
[170, 179, "16-bit integer values, such as flag bits representing DIMSTYLE settings"],
[210, 210, "Extrusion direction (fixed) \n" +
  "DXF: X value of extrusion direction \n" +
  "APP: 3D extrusion direction vector"],
[220, 220, "DXF: Y value of the extrusion direction"],
[230, 230, "DXF: Z value of the extrusion direction"],
[270, 279, "16-bit integer values"],
[280, 289, "16-bit integer value"],
[290, 299, "Boolean flag value; 0 = False; 1 = True"],
[300, 309, "Arbitrary text strings"],
[310, 319, "Arbitrary binary chunks with same representation and limits \n" + 
  "as 1004 group codes: hexadecimal strings of up to 254 characters \n" +
  "represent data chunks of up to 127 bytes"],
[320, 329, "Arbitrary object handles; handle values that are taken 'as is'. \n" +
  "They are not translated during INSERT and XREF operations"],
[330, 339, "Soft-pointer handle; arbitrary soft pointers to other objects \n" +
  "within same DXF file or drawing. Translated during INSERT and XREF operations"],
[340, 349, "Hard-pointer handle; arbitrary hard pointers to other objects within \n" +
  "same DXF file or drawing. Translated during INSERT and XREF operations"],
[350, 359, "Soft-owner handle; arbitrary soft ownership links to other objects \n" +
  "within same DXF file or drawing. Translated during INSERT and XREF operations"],
[360, 369, "Hard-owner handle; arbitrary hard ownership links to other objects within \n" +
  "same DXF file or drawing. Translated during INSERT and XREF operations"],
[370, 379, "Lineweight enum value (AcDb::LineWeight). Stored and moved around as a 16-bit integer. \n" +
  "Custom non-entity objects may use the full range, but entity classes only use 371-379 DXF \n" +
  "group codes in their representation, because AutoCAD and AutoLISP both always assume a 370 \n" +
  "group code is the entity's lineweight. This allows 370 to behave like other 'common' entity fields"],
[380, 389, "PlotStyleName type enum (AcDb::PlotStyleNameType). Stored and moved around as a 16-bit integer.\n" +
  "Custom non-entity objects may use the full range, but entity classes only use 381-389 \n" +
  "DXF group codes in their representation, for the same reason as the Lineweight range"],
[390, 399, "String representing handle value of the PlotStyleName object, basically a hard pointer, but has \n" +
  "a different range to make backward compatibility easier to deal with. Stored and moved around \n" +
  "as an object ID (a handle in DXF files) and a special type in AutoLISP. Custom non-entity objects \n" +
  "may use the full range, but entity classes only use 391-399 DXF group codes in their representation, \n" +
  "for the same reason as the lineweight range"],
[400, 409, "16-bit integers"],
[410, 419, "String"]
[420, 427, "32-bit integer value. When used with True Color; a 32-bit integer representing a 24-bit color value.\n" +
  "The high-order byte (8 bits) is 0, the low-order byte an unsigned char holding the Blue value (0-255), \n" +
  "then the Green value, and the next-to-high order byte is the Red Value. Converting this integer value to \n" +
  "hexadecimal yields the following bit mask: 0x00RRGGBB. \n" +
  "For example, a true color with Red==200, Green==100 and Blue==50 is 0x00C86432, and in DXF, in decimal, 13132850"],
[430, 437, "String; when used for True Color, a string representing the name of the color"],
[440, 447, "32-bit integer value. When used for True Color, the transparency value"],
[450, 459, "Long"],
[460, 469, "Double-precision floating-point value"],
[470, 479, "String"],
[480, 481, "Hard-pointer handle; arbitrary hard pointers to other objects within same DXF file or drawing. \n" +
  "Translated during INSERT and XREF operations \n" +
[999, 999, "DXF: The 999 group code indicates that the line following it is a comment string. SAVEAS does \n" +
  "not include such groups in a DXF output file, but OPEN honors them and ignores the comments. \n"+
  "You can use the 999 group to include comments in a DXF file that you have edited"],
[1000, 1000, "ASCII string (up to 255 bytes long) in extended data"],
[1001, 1001, "Registered application name (ASCII string up to 31 bytes long) for extended data"],
[1002, 1002, "Extended data control string ('{' or '}')"],
[1003, 1003, "Extended data layer name"],
[1004, 1004, "Chunk of bytes (up to 127 bytes long) in extended data"],
[1005, 1005, "Entity handle in extended data; text string of up to 16 hexadecimal digits"],
[1010, 1010, "A point in extended data \n" +
  "DXF: X value (followed by 1020 and 1030 groups) \n" +
  "APP: 3D point"],
[1020, 1020, "DXF: Y values of a point"],
[1030, 1030, "DXF: Z values of a point"],
[1011, 1011, "A 3D world space position in extended data \n" +
  "DXF: X value (followed by 1021 and 1031 groups) \n" +
  "APP: 3D point"],
[1021, 1021, "DXF: Y value of a world space position"],
[1031, 1031, "DXF: Z value of a world space position"],
[1012, 1012, "A 3D world space displacement in extended data \n" +
  "DXF: X value (followed by 1022 and 1032 groups) \n" +
  "APP: 3D vector"],
[1022, 1022, "DXF: Y value of a world space displacement"],
[1032, 1032, "DXF: Z value of a world space displacement"],
[1013, 1013, "A 3D world space direction in extended data \n" +
  "DXF: X value (followed by 1022 and 1032 groups) \n" +
  "APP: 3D vector"],
[1023, 1023, "DXF: Y value of a world space direction"],
[1033, 1033, "DXF: Z value of a world space direction"],
[1040, 1040, "Extended data double-precision floating-point value"],
[1041, 1041, "Extended data distance value"],
[1042, 1042, "Extended data scale factor"],
[1070, 1070, "Extended data 16-bit signed integer"],
[1071, 1071, "Extended data 32-bit signed long"]